{
    "id": "d6e14527beb448ab904b875a0b478387",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Shyam heard the weather report ………………. promptly cancelled the trip.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "so",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "New York is a prosperous city ………………. suffers from many symptoms of urban maladies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "and",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Mike became addicted to drinking – ........................................... that didn’t surprise anybody.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................... you use your credit cards frequently, you will soon find yourself in deep debt.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Everybody ........................................... John was present.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You can work hard for this exam ......................................... you can fail.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "unless",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "................................................. she was the most popular candidate, she lost the election by a large margin.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "But",
                "As"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That is neither ................................................. I said nor what I meant.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Peter thought he would get the job ............................................ his father was on the company’s board of trustees.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "because",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know ............................................. I should study math or physics.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "weather"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}